Now, a lot of places that you can buy supplies for beer pong is actually, go to any convenience store.
Red cups, red Dixie cups are the easiest to play with and they are the most commonly used.
So you can buy those at any liquor store, any convenience store, any grocery store, the little Dixie cups.
Ping pong balls are a little bit harder to find.
Sometimes you can find them in the grocery store in the toy aisle, but other than that a good place is REI or a Sports Authority, something like that is always going to have ping pong balls.
Anywhere that sells sports equipment like that.
So, you need water.
Just fill it up with your sink.
That's really easy.
The beer pong table is actually the most crucial.
If you can't afford to spring for all this stuff that I just showed you in this video, just use a regular table.
It doesn't have to be fancy enough to be cool.
And if you are, if it is too short just make people stand back further to actually shoot.
Please join me again, next time, for all of my other videos.